<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Reproducibilitea Sheffield</title>
<link>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/</link>
<atom:link href="https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description>Details about the Sheffield Reproducibilitea Journal Club</description>
<generator>quarto-1.5.57</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>Reproducibilitea 2024-07-12</title>
  <link>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-07-12/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 





<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><img src="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/research-cycle.svg" class="img-fluid figure-img"></p>
<figcaption>The Turing Way project illustration by Scriberia. Used under a CC-BY 4.0 licence. DOI: <a href="https://doi.org/10.5281/zenodo.3332807">10.5281/zenodo.3332807</a></figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="what" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="what">What</h2>
<p>The chosen article that we will review and discuss is from <a href="https://ojs.aaai.org/index.php/ICWSM/issue/view/459"><em>ICWSM Workshop (2015) Technical Report WS-15-18 (Standards and Practices in Large-Scale Social Media Research) /</em></a></p>
<ul>
<li>Making social media research reproducible (2018). <a href="https://doi.org/10.1609/icwsm.v9i4.14685">doi:10.1609/icwsm.v9i4.14685</a></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="blockquote">
<p>The huge numbers of people using social media makes online social networks an attractive source of data for researchers. But in order for the resultant huge numbers of research publications that involve social media to be credible and trusted, their methodologies, considerations of data handling and sensitivity, analysis, and so forth must be appropriately documented. We believe that one way to improve standards and practices in social media research is to encourage such research to be made reproducible, that is, to have sufficient documentation and sharing of research to allow others to either replicate or build on research results. Enabling this fundamental part of the scientific method will benefit the entire social media ecosystem, from the researchers who use data, to the people that benefit from the outcomes of research.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Ric Campbell (Research Data Steward) will take us through this paper highlighting some salient points and opening discussion.</p>
</section>
<section id="where" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="where">Where</h2>
<p>This event will be hybrid, if you wish to attend in person we will be meeting in Meeting Room 410 of the <a href="https://www.openstreetmap.org/relation/16165929">Arts Tower</a>.</p>
<p>Add the event to your Google Calendar using this <a href="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/event?action=TEMPLATE&amp;tmeid=MWJib3EwbDhoa2U0ZzZmdHFkOHBiMTVtMXEgbi5zaGVwaGFyZEBzaGVmZmllbGQuYWMudWs&amp;tmsrc=n.shephard%40sheffield.ac.uk">link</a>.</p>
<p>If you aren’t able to attend in person but would like to join the Journal Club you can do so using <a href="https://meet.google.com/nio-aheq-gnc">Google Meet</a>.</p>
</section>
<section id="when" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="when">When</h2>
<p>2024-07-12 @ 12:30</p>
</section>
<section id="future-events" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="future-events">Future Events</h2>
<p>To stay abreast of up-coming events you can either sign up to the <a href="https://groups.google.com/a/sheffield.ac.uk/g/reproducibilitea">mailing list</a> or subscribe to the <a href="https://reproducibilitea-sheffield.github.io/index.xml">RSS feed</a>.</p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>reproducibilitea</category>
  <category>reproducibility</category>
  <category>sheffield</category>
  <guid>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-07-12/</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/research-cycle.svg" medium="image" type="image/svg+xml"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Reproducibilitea 2024-05-16</title>
  <link>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-05-16/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 





<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><img src="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/peer-review-process.jpg" class="img-fluid figure-img"></p>
<figcaption>The Turing Way project illustration by Scriberia. Used under a CC-BY 4.0 licence. DOI: <a href="https://doi.org/10.5281/zenodo.3332807">10.5281/zenodo.3332807</a></figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="what" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="what">What</h2>
<p>The chosen article that we will review and discuss is from <em>F1000 Research</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Ten considerations for open peer review (2018). <a href="https://doi.org/10.12688/f1000research.15334.1">doi:10.12688/f1000research.15334.1</a></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="blockquote">
<p>Open peer review (OPR), as with other elements of open science and open research, is on the rise. It aims to bring greater transparency and participation to formal and informal peer review processes. But what is meant by `open peer review’, and what advantages and disadvantages does it have over standard forms of review? How do authors or reviewers approach OPR? And what pitfalls and opportunities should you look out for? Here, we propose ten considerations for OPR, drawing on discussions with authors, reviewers, editors, publishers and librarians, and provide a pragmatic, hands-on introduction to these issues. We cover basic principles and summarise best practices, indicating how to use OPR to achieve best value and mutual benefits for all stakeholders and the wider research community.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Jim Uttley (Lectuer in Architectural Science) will take us through this paper highlighting some salient points and opening discussion.</p>
</section>
<section id="where" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="where">Where</h2>
<p>This event will be hybrid, if you wish to attend in person we will be meeting in Meeting Room G07 of the <a href="https://www.openstreetmap.org/relation/16133670">Hicks Building</a>.</p>
<p>Add the event to your Google Calendar using this <a href="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/event?action=TEMPLATE&amp;tmeid=MmRvZWtlMWhkaXBoazUxa3RtZmEyM2tkbTAgbi5zaGVwaGFyZEBzaGVmZmllbGQuYWMudWs&amp;tmsrc=n.shephard%40sheffield.ac.uk">link</a>.</p>
<p>If you aren’t able to attend in person but would like to join the Journal Club you can do so using <a href="https://meet.google.com/hvf-awcg-uxu">Google Meet</a>.</p>
</section>
<section id="when" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="when">When</h2>
<p>2024-05-16 @ 12:00</p>
</section>
<section id="future-events" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="future-events">Future Events</h2>
<p>To stay abreast of up-coming events you can either sign up to the <a href="https://groups.google.com/a/sheffield.ac.uk/g/reproducibilitea">mailing list</a> or subscribe to the <a href="https://reproducibilitea-sheffield.github.io/index.xml">RSS feed</a>.</p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>reproducibilitea</category>
  <category>reproducibility</category>
  <category>sheffield</category>
  <guid>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-05-16/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/peer-review-process.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Reproducibilitea 2024-04-18</title>
  <link>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-04-18/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 





<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><img src="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/community.svg" class="img-fluid figure-img"></p>
<figcaption>The Turing Way project illustration by Scriberia. Used under a CC-BY 4.0 licence. DOI: <a href="https://doi.org/10.5281/zenodo.3332807">10.5281/zenodo.3332807</a></figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="what" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="what">What</h2>
<p>The chosen articles that we will review and discuss is from <em>Ecology and Evolution</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Accelerating the open research agenda to solve global challenges (2024). <a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/ece3.10887">doi :10.1002/ece3.10887</a></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="blockquote">
<p>Harnessing science-based policy is key to addressing global challenges like the biodiversity and climate crises. Open research principles underpin effective science-based policy, but the uptake of these principles is likely constrained by the politicisation, commoditisation and conflicting motives of stakeholders in the research landscape. Here, using the mission and vision statements from 129 stakeholders from across the research landscape, we explore alignment in open research principles between stakeholders. We find poor alignment between stakeholders, largely focussed around journals, societies and funders, all of which have low open research language-use. We argue that this poor alignment stifles knowledge flow within the research landscape, ultimately limiting the mobilisation of impactful science-based policy. We offer recommendations on how the research landscape could embrace open research principles to accelerate societies’ ability to solve global challenges.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Zuzanna Zagrodzka (PhD Student, Ecology and Evolutionary Biology) will take us through her recently published paper looking at the alignment of open research policy in stakeholders, its impact and recommendations on improving the situation.</p>
</section>
<section id="where" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="where">Where</h2>
<p>This event will be hybrid, if you wish to attend in person we will be meeting in Meeting Room 105 of the <a href="https://www.openstreetmap.org/#map=19/53.38271/-1.48729">The Arts Tower</a>.</p>
<p>Add the event to your Google Calendar using this <a href="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/event?action=TEMPLATE&amp;tmeid=NzF1ODc4M3RlOWJxcmh2Z2xqM2I4bjRzcmYgbi5zaGVwaGFyZEBzaGVmZmllbGQuYWMudWs&amp;tmsrc=n.shephard%40sheffield.ac.uk">link</a>.</p>
<p>If you aren’t able to attend in person but would like to join the Journal Club you can do so using <a href="meet.google.com/gjh-deen-hnk">Google Meet</a>.</p>
</section>
<section id="when" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="when">When</h2>
<p>2024-04-18 @ 14:00</p>
</section>
<section id="future-events" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="future-events">Future Events</h2>
<p>To stay abreast of up-coming events you can either sign up to the <a href="https://groups.google.com/a/sheffield.ac.uk/g/reproducibilitea">mailing list</a> or subscribe to the <a href="https://reproducibilitea-sheffield.github.io/index.xml">RSS feed</a>.</p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>reproducibilitea</category>
  <category>reproducibility</category>
  <category>sheffield</category>
  <guid>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-04-18/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/community.svg" medium="image" type="image/svg+xml"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Reproducibilitea 2024-03-26</title>
  <link>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-03-26/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 





<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><img src="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/evolution-open-research.png" class="img-fluid figure-img"></p>
<figcaption>The Turing Way project illustration by Scriberia. Used under a CC-BY 4.0 licence. DOI: <a href="https://doi.org/10.5281/zenodo.3332807">10.5281/zenodo.3332807</a></figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="what" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="what">What</h2>
<p>The chosen articles that we will review and discuss are from <em>Educational Research and Evaluation</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Replication is relevant to qualitative research (2022). <a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/13803611.2021.2022310">doi : 10.1080/13803611.2021.2022310</a></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="blockquote">
<p>Replication has received increasing attention over the last decade. This comes on the heels of prominent instances of data fabrication (National Academies of Sciences, Engineering, and Medicine, 2017) and estimates that few studies attempt to replicate previous findings (Makel &amp; Plucker, 2014). Replication has been called the Supreme Court of science (Collins, 1985), as well as a basic building block of scholarship. One persistent question in informal conversations that we have not seen addressed in formal writing, is replication’s relevance to qualitative research. Qualitative research is “a situated activity that locates the observer in the world” and “consists of a set of interpretive, material practices that make the world visible” (Denzin &amp; Lincoln, 2011, p.&nbsp;3). Some have argued that replication “missed the point” of qualitative research (Pratt et al., 2020, p.&nbsp;3). However, in a survey of nearly 1,500 recently published education researchers, less than 10% of qualitative researchers reported that replication should never be used (Makel et al., 2021). Given the prevalence of qualitative research in education, it is important to examine replication’s relevance. In this commentary, we argue that replication is relevant to the qualitative lens in at least three ways. First, replication supports the established values in qualitative research of transparency and intentionality. Second, replication can be used to assess the well-established tradition of transferability. Third, replication can evaluate connections between reflexivity, as evidenced by positionality statements, and qualitative research findings.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>…and an article in response…</p>
<ul>
<li>Is replication <em>possible</em> in qualitative research? A response to Makel et al.&nbsp;<a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/13803611.2024.2314526">doi: 10.1080/13803611.2024.2314526</a></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="blockquote">
<p>There has been much debate in recent years about how open research practices, which have been promoted in efforts to improve research robustness, may (not) be appropriate for qualitative methodologies, particularly in educational research. Among these is a concern for replication efforts. Makel et al.&nbsp;(Citation2022) make the case that “replication is relevant to qualitative research”. The authors argue that concerns surrounding the transferability, intentionality, and transparency of qualitative research may be eased, or responded to, by replication studies. Here, I argue that there are three fundamental questions that need unpacking before declarative claims can be made about the relevance of replication to qualitative research. This includes critical questioning of what we mean by: replication, qualitative research, and rigour. I address each of these issues and encourage a more nuanced appraisal of how replication may, or may not, be epistemologically, ontologically, or methodologically compatible with the goals of qualitative research.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Jenni Adams (Open Research Manager, Scholarly Communications Team) will give a brief summary of the article and will open discussion by highlighting some of the points they thought were good/bad about the paper.</p>
</section>
<section id="where" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="where">Where</h2>
<p>This event will be hybrid, if you wish to attend in person we will be meeting in View Room 4 on the 4th Floor of the <a href="https://www.openstreetmap.org/#map=19/53.38172/-1.48222">The Students Union</a>.</p>
<p>Add the event to your Google Calendar using this <a href="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/event?action=TEMPLATE&amp;tmeid=NzF1ODc4M3RlOWJxcmh2Z2xqM2I4bjRzcmYgbi5zaGVwaGFyZEBzaGVmZmllbGQuYWMudWs&amp;tmsrc=n.shephard%40sheffield.ac.uk">link</a>.</p>
<p>If you aren’t able to attend in person but would like to join the Journal Club you can do so using <a href="https://meet.google.com/fdh-whnv-mbv">Google Meet</a>.</p>
</section>
<section id="when" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="when">When</h2>
<p>2024-03-26 @ 12:00</p>
</section>
<section id="future-events" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="future-events">Future Events</h2>
<p>To stay abreast of up-coming events you can either sign up to the <a href="https://groups.google.com/a/sheffield.ac.uk/g/reproducibilitea">mailing list</a> or subscribe to the <a href="https://reproducibilitea-sheffield.github.io/index.xml">RSS feed</a>.</p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>reproducibilitea</category>
  <category>reproducibility</category>
  <category>sheffield</category>
  <guid>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-03-26/</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/evolution-open-research.png" medium="image" type="image/png"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Reproducibilitea 2024-01-18</title>
  <link>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-01-18/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 





<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><img src="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/research-compendium.svg" class="img-fluid figure-img"></p>
<figcaption>The Turing Way project illustration by Scriberia. Used under a CC-BY 4.0 licence. DOI: <a href="https://doi.org/10.5281/zenodo.3332807">10.5281/zenodo.3332807</a></figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="what" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="what">What</h2>
<p>The chosen article to that we will review and discuss is an essay from <em>The Journal of Electronic Publishing</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Pooley J. Surveillance Publishing <em>The Journal of Electronic Publishing</em> (2022). <a href="https://doi.org/10.3998/jep.1874">doi : 10.3998/jep.1874</a></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="blockquote">
<p>This essay develops the idea of surveillance publishing, with special attention to the example of Elsevier. A scholarly publisher can be defined as a surveillance publisher if it derives a substantial proportion of its revenue from prediction products, fueled by data extracted from researcher behavior. The essay begins by tracing the Google search engine’s roots in bibliometrics, alongside a history of the citation analysis company that became, in 2016, Clarivate. The essay develops the idea of surveillance publishing by engaging with the work of Shoshana Zuboff, Jathan Sadowski, Mariano-Florentino Cuéllar, and Aziz Huq. The recent history of Elsevier is traced to describe the company’s research-lifecycle data-harvesting strategy, with the aim to develop and sell prediction products to unviersity and other customers. The essay concludes by considering some of the potential costs of surveillance publishing, as other big commercial publishers increasingly enter the predictive-analytics business. It is likely, I argue, that windfall subscription-and-APC profits in Elsevier’s “legacy” publishing business have financed its decade-long acquisition binge in analytics. The products’ purpose, moreover, is to streamline the top-down assessment and evaluation practices that have taken hold in recent decades. A final concern is that scholars will internalize an analytics mindset, one already encouraged by citation counts and impact factors.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Adam Partridge (Open Research Training Lead / ELIXIR-UK DaSH Fellow at University of Sheffield) will give a brief summary of the article and will open discussion by highlighting some of the points he thought were good/bad about the paper.</p>
</section>
<section id="where" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="where">Where</h2>
<p>This event will be hybrid, if you wish to attend in person we will be meeting in Meeting Room 1 of <a href="https://www.openstreetmap.org/#map=19/53.38172/-1.48222">The Diamond, 32 Leavygreave Road, Sheffield, Broomhall, S3 7RD</a>.</p>
<p>Add the event to your Google Calendar using this <a href="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/event?action=TEMPLATE&amp;tmeid=MnV2YmI4OGdtYjhwaDBuaWkyMWUwaGNrbTkgbi5zaGVwaGFyZEBzaGVmZmllbGQuYWMudWs&amp;tmsrc=n.shephard%40sheffield.ac.uk">link</a>.</p>
<p>If you aren’t able to attend in person but would like to join the Journal Club you can do so using <a href="https://meet.google.com/ira-xqvm-qpt">Google Meet</a>.</p>
</section>
<section id="when" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="when">When</h2>
<p>2024-01-18 @ 12:00</p>
</section>
<section id="future-events" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="future-events">Future Events</h2>
<p>To stay abreast of up-coming events you can either sign up to the <a href="https://groups.google.com/a/sheffield.ac.uk/g/reproducibilitea">mailing list</a> or subscribe to the <a href="https://reproducibilitea-sheffield.github.io/index.xml">RSS feed</a>.</p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>reproducibilitea</category>
  <category>reproducibility</category>
  <category>sheffield</category>
  <guid>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2024-01-18/</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/research-compendium.svg" medium="image" type="image/svg+xml"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Reproducibilitea 2023-12-06</title>
  <link>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2023-12/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 





<div class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center">
<figure class="figure">
<p><img src="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/reproducibility.jpg" class="img-fluid figure-img"></p>
<figcaption>The Turing Way project illustration by Scriberia. Used under a CC-BY 4.0 licence. DOI: <a href="https://doi.org/10.5281/zenodo.3332807">10.5281/zenodo.3332807</a></figcaption>
</figure>
</div>
<section id="what" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="what">What</h2>
<p>The chosen article to that we review and discuss is a recent publication <em>Nature Human Behaviour</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Protzko, J., Krosnick, J., Nelson, L. et al.&nbsp;High replicability of newly discovered social-behavioural findings is achievable. Nat Hum Behav (2023). <a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41562-023-01749-9">doi : 10.1038/s41562-023-01749-9</a></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="blockquote">
<p>Failures to replicate evidence of new discoveries have forced scientists to ask whether this unreliability is due to suboptimal implementation of methods or whether presumptively optimal methods are not, in fact, optimal. This paper reports an investigation by four coordinated laboratories of the prospective replicability of 16 novel experimental findings using rigour-enhancing practices: confirmatory tests, large sample sizes, preregistration and methodological transparency. In contrast to past systematic replication efforts that reported replication rates averaging 50%, replication attempts here produced the expected effects with significance testing (P &lt; 0.05) in 86% of attempts, slightly exceeding the maximum expected replicability based on observed effect sizes and sample sizes. When one lab attempted to replicate an effect discovered by another lab, the effect size in the replications was 97% that in the original study. This high replication rate justifies confidence in rigour-enhancing methods to increase the replicability of new discoveries.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Neil Shephard (Research Software Engineer at University of Sheffield) will give a brief summary of the article and will open discussion by highlighting some of the points he thought were good/bad about the paper.</p>
</section>
<section id="where" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="where">Where</h2>
<p>This event will be hybrid, if you wish to attend in person we will be meeting in Workroom 2 of <a href="https://www.openstreetmap.org/#map=19/53.38172/-1.48222">The Diamond, 32 Leavygreave Road, Sheffield, Broomhall, S3 7RD</a>.</p>
<p>Add the event to your Google Calendar using this <a href="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/event?action=TEMPLATE&amp;tmeid=MjU3NmE5dWlpbHUydTQ0Y2YzOWFzYmdkM2ggbi5zaGVwaGFyZEBzaGVmZmllbGQuYWMudWs&amp;tmsrc=n.shephard%40sheffield.ac.uk">link</a>.</p>
<p>If you aren’t able to attend in person but would like to join the Journal Club you can do so using <a href="https://meet.google.com/ehu-zapk-awt">Google Meet</a>.</p>
</section>
<section id="when" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="when">When</h2>
<p>2023-12-06 @ 13:15 Sheffield Reproducibilitea Journal Club is back in time to see 2023 out.</p>
</section>
<section id="future-events" class="level2">
<h2 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="future-events">Future Events</h2>
<p>To stay abreast of up-coming events you can either sign up to the <a href="https://groups.google.com/a/sheffield.ac.uk/g/reproducibilitea">mailing list</a> or subscribe to the <a href="https://reproducibilitea-sheffield.github.io/index.xml">RSS feed</a>.</p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>reproducibilitea</category>
  <category>reproducibility</category>
  <category>sheffield</category>
  <guid>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/2023-12/</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://the-turing-way.netlify.app/_images/reproducibility.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Reproducibilitea Sheffield Reboot</title>
  <link>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/reboot/</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 





<p>Reproducibilitea Sheffield is back!</p>
<p>This site will hold details of up-coming Journal Clubs and provides links to useful resources.</p>
<p>To stay abreast of up-coming events you can either sign up to the <a href="https://groups.google.com/a/sheffield.ac.uk/g/reproducibilitea">mailing list</a> or subscribe to the <a href="https://reproducibilitea-sheffield.github.io/index.xml">RSS feed</a>.</p>



 ]]></description>
  <category>reproducibilitea</category>
  <category>reproducibility</category>
  <category>sheffield</category>
  <guid>https://Reproducibilitea-Sheffield.github.io/posts/reboot/</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/bf/ab/0a/bfab0acb4ef0ab8edb7863bcfddd0a7c.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
